about me

I'm a strong minded, hard working individual. I've always strived to to my best in anything I do. I posses 13 years in the hospitality industry(last 5 in Mgmt). I'm charismatic and professional with a passion for....****CODE****. Checkout my Github Acc. https://github.com/newbsaibot. I left my hospitality management career a year ago to focus on my love and passion for programming and web development. I've been teaching myself programming for the last 4 years. I started with Python (still work with Python) and have currently moved onto working with C# and Unity for game development, Kali Linux, learning basic commands on the terminal preparing for ethical hacking and Arduino which I've got to say I've had a blast with! Im comfortable with Python, C#, and JavaScript. I'm currently and usually always taking multiple tutorials which has given me tons of exposure to several different tools and languages from online resources including Team Tree House, udemy, Codeacademy, Freecodecamp, Youtube, Google, Stack Overflow and countless tutorials across the net. I'm looking to become a junior/intermediate developer with a team that posses the love and passion that I have for code. It's all I think about, it's all I want to do. I'd love to do what I love with a team that loves it too.:)

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

employment history

QooQee

Front end developer (temp)

June 2018 - September 2018

Worked with webFlow and duplicated current projects used with muse as a transfer method. Worked with html and css slightly to accommodate webFlows short comings. Projects were all templates with several pages including home, extras, contact form which I replicated using webflow as required. Great learning experience unfortunately it was a short term contract.

SURFER [THE BAR]

General Manager (GM)

November 2016 - February 2018

While opening Surfer [The Bar] My responsibilities throughout the opening were to interview all potential employees for both FOH and BOH. I created the training agenda for all FOH staff as well as their specialty cocktail menu test. The ongoing development of all staff members as well as scheduling for all departments. The training of first time and experienced managers to create a larger management team as there was only Three managers, I was always relied on the most as I am the most experienced among the Management team. I was contracted as acting GM. Overseeing daily operations, and assuring that all team members we trained to spec in order to assure the smoothest opening for the Bar. Weekly labor reports adjusted accordingly and sent out for payroll purposes and working with a Labor pro where I projected and kept track of our budgeting using a declining budget. Manage 100+ employees in a high volume record breaking sales compared to our sister bars with over \$100,00 in sales weekly.

Hawkers Asian Street Fare

Assistant General Manager

November 2011 - October 2016

Fluent in both English and Spanish both written and verbal. Intermediate in Excel, Python, Java, JavaScript, C#, BootStrap, Unity, Arduino programming languages, as well as HTML and CSS. Inventory control and record keeping. Strong work ethic, Results-oriented, Knowledge of POS systems including Restaurant Manager, Aloha, 2Touch, Micros and restaurant manager. Knowledge of assigning job codes, pay rates, and start dates on back end POS systems. Comprehension of P&L reports as well as E.B.I.T and E.B.I.T.A. reports. Experience using Hot Schedules scheduling software (4 years)

education

Miami-Dade-College

Associates in Network Engineering

Graduated December 2007

hobbies & interests

Arduino (Electrical Engineering Projects(personal), Research more about Programming, Tutorials on Ed-x and several other online tracks. Honestly I just love to code, besides that, spending time with my fiance' and taking the dog to the park and eating asian food everywhere, oh! and of course COFFEE!!!

professional skills

Webflow Intermediate
HTML5 Intermediate
CSS Competent

languages

Python Proficient
Java Beginner
Javascript Beginner

references

Eric Chan

Superior

Shary Junco

Art Director/UI & UX Manager

Casey Buckley

Superior